Ariel Curtido

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Profile

I'm a Software Engineer with 10 years of work experience in the software industry. Broad knowledge of mission critical and complementary software, such as ERP, migration tools and reporting. I'm currently focused on web development, being my main past job expertise field.

Work Experience

Full Stack Developer, CBA, Asunción

2019 — PRESENT

- Effectively translated client needs into application designs and system requirements.
- Maintain and add features to a legacy ERP based on design specifications.
- Collaborated to create strategic initiatives to design and code solutions.
- Helped to achieve a consistent visual theme of the software by promoting uniform layouts.
- Main technologies: Python Django, Django Rest Framework, React JS, Oracle, Jasper Report.

Full Stack Developer, Exxis Group, Asunción

2018 — 2019

- · Analyzed and designed an extension for SAP Business One.
- Created, communicated, and managed project plans.
- Worked with SAP development tools, techniques, and approaches.
- Main technologies: ASP.NET C#, Windows Forms, SQL Server, Crystal Reports, SAP ERP, SAP Hana, SAP DI-API and SAP UI-API.

Developer, CBA, Asunción

2013 — 2018

- Helped to provide local industry-leading solutions with ERP software.
- Effectively multi-tasked and worked well in multiple projects.
- Worked to continually meet the customers' expectations.
- Main technologies: ASP.NET C#, Classic ASP, Crystal Report, Oracle, LaTeX.

Education

Software Engineer Degree, <u>Columbia University of Paraguay</u>, Asunción

2011 — 2017

Graduated with High Honors

Details

Ñemby, Paraguay +595971796306 aicurtido@gmail.com

PLACE OF BIRTH

Asunción, Paraguay

Links

<u>LinkedIn Profile</u> <u>GitHub</u>

Skills

Python

Node.js

C#

SQL

AWS/Azure

Data Analytics

Ability to Work in a Team

Customer Service

Communication Skills

Languages

Spanish Native speaker

English
Highly proficient

Portuguese
Good working knowledge